Guide to the University of Chicago Office of the President, Kimpton Administration Records 1892-1960
University of Chicago Library
- Series I: General Files
  - U.S. Army Reserve centers, 408th and 486th Strategic Intelligence Detachments, 1953-1954 (Box 284, Folder 5)
  - Vanderbilt University, 1959-1960 (Box 284, Folder 6)
  - Veterans Administration, correspondence and contracts, 1944-1957 (Box 284, Folder 7)
  - Veterans Nursery School, 1946-1956 (Box 284, Folder 8)
  - Veterans testing and counseling, 1944-1955 (Box 284, Folder 9)
  - V, general, 1950-1955 (Box 284, Folder 10)
  - Vice-Chancellor for Administration, John Irvine Kirkpatrick, 1959-1960 (Box 284, Folder 11)
  - Vice President of Development, 1951-1960 (Box 284, Folder 12)
  - Vice President in Charge of Business Affairs, James A. Cunningham, 1953 (Box 284, Folder 13)
  - Vice-President of the University, Filbey, Emery Thomas, 1957-1960 (Box 284, Folder 14)
  - Vice-President of the University, Filbey, Emery Thomas, fiftieth anniversary of service, 1959 (Box 284, Folder 15)
  - Visiting committees, general, 1952-1959 (Box 284, Folder 16)
  - "Voice of America," 1958 (Box 284, Folder 17)
  - Voting Registration Study, Science Research Associates, 1955 (Box 284, Folder 18)
  - War, 1940-1958 (Box 284, Folder 19)
  - Wars, University participation, Spanish-American, World War I, World War II, Korean and post-Korean War periods, 1898-1955 (Box 284, Folder 20)
  - Wars, University participation 1898-1955, Spanish-American, World War I, World War II, Korean and post-Korean War periods (Box 285, Folder 1-2)
  - Washington, D.C., Representative, 1941-1953 (Box 285, Folder 3)
  - Washington University, St. Louis, Missouri, 1946-1959 (Box 285, Folder 4)
  - Washington, University of, 1955-1960 (Box 285, Folder 5)
  - Wayne State University, 1954-1958 (Box 285, Folder 6)
  - Weiss, Trevor, Modified Insurance Plan, 1959-1960 (Box 285, Folder 7)
  - Welfare Council of Metropolitan Chicago, 1949-1960 (Box 285, Folder 8-9)
  - West African Countries, Conference to Discuss Problems, Sponsoring Committee, August 31-September 4, 1960 (Box 285, Folder 10)
  - West Metropolitan Area Council, Incorporated, 1955 (Box 285, Folder 11)
  - West Suburban Hospital, 1957 (Box 285, Folder 12)
  - Western Association of College and University Business Officers, 1954-1959 (Box 285, Folder 13)
  - Westwood Hills (California) Christian Church, 1955 (Box 285, Folder 14)
  - W, general, 1950-1955 (Box 285, Folder 15)
  - White House Conference on Health, 1956-1959 (Box 285, Folder 16)
  - Who's Who in American Education, 1956-1959 (Box 285, Folder 17)
  - Wilson, Mount, and Palomar Observatories, 1955-1956 (Box 285, Folder 18)
  - Wilson, Woodrow, Fellowship Program, 1951-1955 (Box 285, Folder 19)
  - Wilson, Woodrow, Fellowship Program, 1954-1959 (Box 286, Folder 1)
  - Wisconsin Alumni Research Foundation, 1956-1957 (Box 286, Folder 2)
  - Wisconsin, University of, 1957-1960 (Box 286, Folder 3-4)
  - Women’s Board of the University of Chicago, membership invitations and correspondence, 1960 (Box 286, Folder 5)
  - Women's Center, College, Quadrangles, proposed, 1952-1957 (Box 286, Folder 6)
  - Woodlawn Boys Club, 1960 (Box 286, Folder 7)
  - World Brotherhood Conference, Conference on World Tensions, May 11-13, 1960, 1959-1960 (Box 286, Folder 8)
  - World Brotherhood Conference, Conference on World Tensions, programs, press releases, speeches, 1960 (Box 286, Folder 9-11)
  - World Brotherhood Conference, Conference on World Tensions, programs, press releases, speeches, 1960 (Box 287, Folder 1)
  - World Brotherhood, Incorporated, 1959-1960 (Box 287, Folder 2)
  - World Health Organization, 1947-1960 (Box 287, Folder 3-4)
  - World Press Congress, 1959 (Box 287, Folder 5)
  - World University Service, 1942-1959 (Box 287, Folder 6)
  - World War II, metallurgical laboratory, 1952 (Box 287, Folder 7)
  - Yale University, 1951-1960 (Box 287, Folder 8-11)
  - Year-end mailings, 1953-1960 (Box 287, Folder 12)
  - Y.M.C.A., 1958-1960 (Box 287, Folder 13)
  - Young Men’s Christian Organization, 1956-1960 (Box 288, Folder 1-2)
  - Young Women's Christian Association, 1953-1959 (Box 288, Folder 3)
  - Yugoslavia, visitors from, 1960 (Box 288, Folder 4)
  - Zoology, Department of, 1946-1960 (Box 288, Folder 5-9)
- Series II: Appointments and Budgets
  - Administration, 1952-1953 (Box 288, Folder 10)
  - Appointment contracts, 1952-1953 (Box 288, Folder 11)
  - Appointments, 1951-1952 (Box 288, Folder 12)
  - Appointments, 1952-1953 (Box 288, Folder 13)
  - Auxiliary enterprises, 1953-1954 (Box 288, Folder 14)
  - Auxiliary enterprises, 1954-1955 (Box 288, Folder 15)
  - Biological Sciences, Division of, 1952-1953 (Box 288, Folder 16-17)
  - Biological Sciences, Division of, 1952-1955 (Box 289, Folder 1-5)
  - Biological Sciences, Division of, 1954-1955 (Box 290, Folder 1-2)
  - Biological Sciences, Division of, Development Office, 1955-1959 (Box 290, Folder 3)
  - Budget, 1951-1953 (Box 290, Folder 4-6)
  - Budget, 1952-1953 (Box 291, Folder 1-4)
  - Budget, 1953-1954 (Box 292, Folder 1-4)
  - Budget, 1954-1956 (Box 293, Folder 1-3)
  - Budget, 1956-1958 (Box 294, Folder 1-2)
  - Budget, 1958-1960 (Box 295, Folder 1-2)
  - Budget, 1960-1961 (Box 296, Folder 1)
  - Budget, Alumni Association, 1951-1954 (Box 296, Folder 2)
  - Budget Committee, 1951-1955 (Box 296, Folder 3-4)
  - Budget, comparative studies, 1954-1955 (Box 296, Folder 5)
  - Budget, letters, 1952-1953 (Box 296, Folder 6)
  - Budget, mid-year revision, 1951-1952 (Box 296, Folder 7)
  - Budget, miscellaneous, 1951-1952 (Box 296, Folder 8)
  - Budget report, 1952-1953 (Box 297, Folder 1)
  - Budget, revision, 1952-1955 (Box 297, Folder 2-4)
  - Budget, Round Table, University of Chicago, 1952-1953 (Box 297, Folder 5)
  - Budget, schedules and general, 1953-1954 (Box 297, Folder 6)
  - Building projects, 1958-1960 (Box 297, Folder 7)
  - Bursar, budget, 1952-1953 (Box 297, Folder 8)
  - Business, 1953-1954 (Box 297, Folder 9)
  - Business Affairs, 1953-1955 (Box 297, Folder 10-11)
  - Business Affairs, contingency, 1951-1952 (Box 297, Folder 12)
  - Business Affairs, Vice President, 1951-1953 (Box 297, Folder 13)
  - Business school, 1951-1953 (Box 297, Folder 14-16)
  - Business School, 1953-1955 (Box 298, Folder 1-2)
  - Chancellor, 1954-1955 (Box 298, Folder 3)
  - Chapel, 1953-1955 (Box 298, Folder 4-5)
  - College, 1951-1954 (Box 298, Folder 6-11)
  - College, 1954-1955 (Box 299, Folder 1-2)
  - Comptroller, 1952-1955 (Box 299, Folder 3-5)
  - Contingency, 1953-1955 (Box 299, Folder 6-7)
  - Dean of Students, 1951-1955 (Box 299, Folder 8-12)
  - Development Office, 1951-1960 (Box 299, Folder 13-14)
  - Development office, budget, 1955-1959 (Box 299, Folder 15-18)
  - Divinity school, 1952-1955 (Box 299, Folder 19-22)
  - Examiner, Office of, 1951-1955 (Box 300, Folder 1-4)
  - Faculty appointments and changes in appointments, 1954 (Box 300, Folder 5-6)
  - Faculty, tenure, 1951 (Box 300, Folder 7)
  - Federated Theological Faculty and Divinity School, 1953-1954 (Box 300, Folder 8)
  - Forms and letters, 1954-1955 (Box 300, Folder 9)
  - Frankfurt, ledger sheets, 1952-1953 (Box 300, Folder 10)
  - Graduate library school, 1952-1953 (Box 300, Folder 11)
  - Harper Library, 1951-1952 (Box 300, Folder 12)
  - Humanities, Division of, 1951-1952 (Box 300, Folder 13)
  - Humanities, Division of, 1952-1955 (Box 301, Folder 1-5)
  - Humanities, Division of, Antonio G. Borges, 1951-1952 (Box 301, Folder 6)
  - Humanities, Division of, budget, 1954-1955 (Box 301, Folder 7)
  - International Educational Exchange Programs, Exchange Visitors’ Program, 1951-1960 (Box 301, Folder 8)
  - International Educational Exchange Programs, Exchange Visitors’ Program, immigration laws and rulings, 1951-1960 (Box 301, Folder 9)
  - International House, budget operations, quarterly statements, 1952-1954 (Box 302, Folder 1)
  - Laboratory School, 1954-1955 (Box 302, Folder 2)
  - Law School, 1951-1955 (Box 302, Folder 3-6)
  - Library, 1952-1954 (Box 302, Folder 7-8)
  - Library School, Graduate, 1953-1955 (Box 302, Folder 9-10)
  - Marshals and Aides, 1951 (Box 302, Folder 11)
  - Measure, A Critical Journal, 1951-1952 (Box 302, Folder 12)
  - Medical School and Clinics, new appointments, change in status, leaving staff, reports, 1950-1956 (Box 303, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous, 1951-1953 (Box 303, Folder 2)
  - Moody, membership, 1951-1953 (Box 303, Folder 3)
  - Nursery school, 1954-1955 (Box 303, Folder 4)
  - Oriental Institute, 1951-1955 (Box 303, Folder 5-9)
  - Orthogenic School, 1954-1955 (Box 303, Folder 10)
  - Personnel office, 1952-1953 (Box 303, Folder 11)
  - Physical Sciences, Division of, 1951-1952 (Box 303, Folder 12-13)
  - Physical Sciences, Division of, 1952-1955 (Box 304, Folder 1-5)
  - Precollegiate education, 1953-1954 (Box 304, Folder 6)
  - Press, 1952-1955 (Box 304, Folder 7-9)
  - Press, Couch, William, dismissal, 1951-1952 (Box 305, Folder 1)
  - Press, journals, 1960 (Box 305, Folder 2)
  - Press, journals published, 1952-1957 (Box 305, Folder 3)
  - Press, journals published, Astrophysical Journal, 1951 (Box 305, Folder 4)
  - Press, journals published, Astrophysical Journal, editors, 1951-1959 (Box 305, Folder 5)
  - Press, journals published, Botanical Gazette, 1959 (Box 305, Folder 6)
  - Press, journals published, Elementary School Journal, 1942-1955 (Box 305, Folder 7)
  - Press, journals published, Journal of Law and Economics, 1958 (Box 305, Folder 8)
  - Press, journals published, Journal of Modern History, 1956 (Box 305, Folder 9)
  - Press, journals published, Journal of Religion, 1954 (Box 305, Folder 10)
  - Press, journals published, Library Quarterly, 1952-1956 (Box 305, Folder 11)
  - Press, journals published, Perspectives in Biology and Medicine, 1958-1960 (Box 305, Folder 12)
  - Press, journals published, Physiological Zoology, 1955 (Box 305, Folder 13)
  - Press, journals published, School Review, 1954-1957 (Box 305, Folder 14)
  - Press, journals published, Social Service Review, 1953-1956 (Box 305, Folder 15)
  - Press, policies, practices and procedures, 1951-1959 (Box 305, Folder 16)
  - Press, Publication Department, summary of receipts and expenses, 1949-1954 (Box 305, Folder 17-18)
  - Publications, Board of University, membership, 1951 (Box 305, Folder 19)
  - Radio Board, membership, 1951 (Box 305, Folder 20)
  - Radio Office, 1954-1955 (Box 305, Folder 21)
  - Restricted expendable, 1953-1954 (Box 305, Folder 22)
  - Rockefeller Chapel, 1952-1954 (Box 305, Folder 23-24)
  - Rockefeller Memorial Chapel, associate deanship and acting deanship, W. Barnett Blakemore, 1959-1960 (Box 305, Folder 25)
  - Salaries, wages, and other compensations, faculty salaries and compensation, 1960 (Box 306, Folder 1)
  - Schedules and general, 1954-1955 (Box 306, Folder 2)
  - Secretary of the Board, 1952-1954 (Box 306, Folder 3-4)
  - Secretary of the University, 1953-1955 (Box 306, Folder 5-6)
  - Social Sciences, Division of, 1950-1954 (Box 306, Folder 7-11)
  - Social Sciences, Division of, 1953-1955 (Box 307, Folder 1-3)
  - Social Sciences, Division of, Committee on Social Thought, 1945-1951 (Box 307, Folder 4)
  - Social Service Administration, School of, 1952-1955 (Box 307, Folder 5-8)
  - Special accounts, 1952 (Box 308, Folder 1)
  - Staff meeting, 1951 (Box 308, Folder 2)
  - Student aid, 1953-1955 (Box 308, Folder 3-4)
  - Student fees, 1951-1952 (Box 308, Folder 5)
  - Sub-collegiate areas, 1952-1954 (Box 308, Folder 6-7)
  - Summer school, 1952-1954 (Box 308, Folder 8-9)
  - Treasurer, 1952-1955 (Box 308, Folder 10-12)
  - University examiner, 1954-1955 (Box 308, Folder 13)
  - University extension, 1952-1955 (Box 308, Folder 14-16)
  - White, Alexander, Visiting Professorships, 1951 (Box 308, Folder 17)
- Series III: Invitations
  - Invitations, 1953-1958 (Box 308, Folder 18-25)
  - Invitations, 1958-1959 (Box 309, Folder 1-10)
  - Invitations, 1959-1960 (Box 310, Folder 1-12)
  - Invitations, 1960 (Box 311, Folder 1-3)
- Series IV: Audiovisual Materials
  - Slides on Hyde Park urban renewal, 1960 (Box 311, Folder 4)